<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business Rental on TWEECORE - Docs</title><link>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/</link><description>Recent content in Business Rental on TWEECORE - Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setup BusinessRental</title><link>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rent_setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rent_setup/</guid><description>The setup should be mostly done by the wizard when installing the extension, but we would like to talk about specifics here. To do this, search for Rental Setup and call the page.
Credit warning - this is where you specify whether you want to receive a warning when credit limits are reached. You already know this setup from the standard.
Shipment on invoice - defines whether a posted shipment and a posted invoice are automatically created when posting an invoice.</description></item><item><title>The rental role center</title><link>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rolecenter/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rolecenter/</guid><description>If you have already assigned yourself the role &amp;ldquo;Rental&amp;rdquo; in your settings, you will see a customized view. From this home page, you can centrally access and manage all rental-related processes.
In the bar at the top, you can quickly access your inventory or the current rental offers and contracts, or you can view your rental-related documents via the posted receipts. On the top right, via Actions, you can create a new rental contract or a new rental offer with one click.</description></item><item><title>Creating itmems, main rental itmes and rental itmes.</title><link>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rent_item/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rent_item/</guid><description>To rent out an item, you need a main rental item and a rental item that references the main rental item. To create a rental item, call up the list of items that you already know from the standard system.
Create a new item here that you want to rent out. Depending on the template, certain values may already be filled in, such as the product booking group. If this is not the case, please make a selection here.</description></item><item><title>Rental Item Attachments</title><link>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rental_item_attachments/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rental_item_attachments/</guid><description>If you want to track which accessories you have handed over to the customer for your rental items, you can use this function in Business Rental. The use is optional.
Open any rental item and select Rental Item Attachments. A corresponding table will open. Here you can define the items that should be handed over again after the rental.
For certain accessories, it may be useful to set the setup to &amp;ldquo;non inventory&amp;rdquo;.</description></item><item><title>Asset accounting</title><link>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/fixed_assets/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/fixed_assets/</guid><description>If you are reading this section, you are most likely dealing with financial and fixed asset accounting in your business.
In accounting, fixed assets are those assets that are shown on the assets side of a balance sheet and are intended to serve the business operations of a company on a permanent basis. Current assets in companies are all assets that are intended for short-term sale, consumption, processing, further processing or repayment as part of the business process.</description></item><item><title>Rental calendars and billing periods.</title><link>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rent_calendar/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rent_calendar/</guid><description>Setting up different rental calendars is necessary whenever you work with different rental rates. For example, for a rental rate that includes weekend billing, you need to create a rental rate and a calendar that allows this billing method. However, you can also configure a monthly flat rate where the price is always the same and it does not matter whether the month has 28 or 31 days.
Example of a day-based billing without calculation of weekends and holidays: Create a new rental tariff for this purpose.</description></item><item><title>Preparation of a rental offer</title><link>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rent_quote/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rent_quote/</guid><description>The basic setup is now complete. You have items that you can rent out, the prices are set. You also know when and how billing will occur. Now let&amp;rsquo;s move on to creating a rental offer.
Click on Rental Offer on the home page or search for the item Rental Offer:
.
A page will now open, here you can first select the customer to which you want to assign the offer.</description></item><item><title>Create rental contract</title><link>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rent_contract/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rent_contract/</guid><description>There are three ways to create a lease. You can create a new rent contract by hand.
Or you can use the function from the rental offer and convert a rental offer into a rental agreement.
If a similar document already exists, copy an existing rental related document. very similar possibility you already know from the standard.
To map the whole process, in our example we create a rental agreement without the copy function or the conversion via a rental offer.</description></item><item><title>Creation of a rent credit</title><link>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rent_creditmemo/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/business-rental/rent_creditmemo/</guid><description>Basically, there are several ways to create a rent credit memo. We will start with the manual creation of a rent credit note as an example.
Procedure for manual rent credit memo To do this, search for Rent Credit Memo in the search and then select New. Select the customer who is to receive the rent credit memo.
In the lines you can select the rental item for which the rental credit memo should be created.</description></item></channel></rss>