<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Project Invoice on TWEECORE - Docs</title><link>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/project-invoice/</link><description>Recent content in Project Invoice on TWEECORE - Docs</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>de-de</language><atom:link href="https://docs.tweecore.de/english/project-invoice/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setting up BC Project Invoice</title><link>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/project-invoice/setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/project-invoice/setup/</guid><description>With Project Invoice from TWEECORE, you can generate your times to be invoiced for your project management tools in Business Central at the touch of a button. However, a set-up is necessary for this. Use the supported setup to be guided through the settings by two simple pages.
Select the item Project Invoice from the list.
Here you can make various presettings. You may want to create a new dedicated number series, but you can also use one that is already in use for your invoices.</description></item><item><title>Project Invoice Setup - Assisted Setup</title><link>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/project-invoice/assistedsetup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/project-invoice/assistedsetup/</guid><description>The easiest way to configure Project Invoice is to use the assisted setup.
Step 1: Invoice Type - this is the sales line type which will be used to be invoiced.
No. - this is the No. which will be used, G/L Account No., Item No. or the Ressource No. .
No. Series for Project Invoices - the No. Series will be used to create the imports from your project management system.</description></item><item><title>Project creation</title><link>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/project-invoice/project_setup/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/project-invoice/project_setup/</guid><description>For the first invoicing or after a new project management tool has been introduced, the projects must be imported at the beginning. This is done via the Project Invoice Projects page. You can enter this page in the Business Central search and call it up.
Then select &amp;ldquo;Import Projects&amp;rdquo;. Each individual project can now be assigned to a client, simply select a project and click on edit.
General On the respective project page, the respective project can be permanently assigned to a specific client.</description></item><item><title>Importing the hours to be accounted for</title><link>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/project-invoice/import_hours/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://docs.tweecore.de/english/project-invoice/import_hours/</guid><description>To retrieve the hours to be billed, call up the action Import Project Hours. A page opens where you can set the billing start date and end date. In addition, you can, for example, set a filter for the creator of the invoice line.
The import is now done, so we can now turn to the lines. To do this, please go to one of the different projects where we will now look at the lines.</description></item></channel></rss>